smallseotool.com 2015-12-24

# Privacy

We encourage you to read this Policy carefully. If you have any questions about this Policy, our use of your Personal Information, or your dealings with this website, please feel free to contact us. We may update this Policy from time to time in our sole discretion to reflect changes in our use of your Personal Information and/or applicable law. Any changes made to this Policy will be reflected in an updated policy (denoted by an updated date above) posted on our website at SmallSeoTools.com. 

SmallSeoTools.com Customer Privacy

Collection of Personal Information

Customers who use the products and services available through our website (collectively, the “Services”) do so voluntarily. In order to use our Services, a customer is required to create an account by registering and providing us with basic contact, billing and website information, including, but not limited to, such customer’s name, email address, credit card information and website URL. By providing us with Personal Information, customers are consenting to the collection, use and disclosure of such Personal Information in accordance with the terms and conditions set forth in this Policy.

How We Use Personal Information

Any Personal Information collected and stored by us is used strictly for billing purposes, contacting our customers, evaluating a prospective customer’s website content, and for such other purposes as are described in this Policy. SmallSeoTools.com does not share any customer Personal Information with any third party other than those business partners which are directly involved in managing our day to day business operations, such as, without limitation, our billing and payment processes. We reserves the right to disclose your Personal Information without notice or consent as it deems necessary (a) to conform to applicable law; (b) when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and property; (c) to protect the safety of our users, us, or other third parties; (d) to comply with any judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on us; and/or (e) pursuant to an acquisition, merger, sale of assets or other business transfer.

Direct Email

Our customers may voluntarily elect to receive their websites’ statistical information via email. We may from time to time include important news, information, or offers within these emails. However, you may choose to opt-out of receiving any such emails, or change the frequency with which you receive such e-mails, at any time by logging on to your personal account page and changing the applicable preferences contained therein

Log Files

By accessing our website, our internet servers automatically record information that your internet browser sends when you visit a website. These logs may contain information such as your internet protocol (IP) address, browser version, domain name, language, date and time, the referring website and information in your cookie files.

Third Party Advertisements

The advertisements appearing on our website from time to time are provided by a variety of our third party advertising partners. We only share website usage information about our users with reputable third party advertisers for the sole purpose of better targeting our website banner advertisements.

SmallSeoTools.com Website Cookies

To allow our customers the convenience of not having to remember their login information when accessing our website, SmallSeoTools.com may place a temporary or persistent “cookie” on your computer’s hard drive. These cookies are simple, harmless text files that remember the internet browser you use to access the internet. However, if you do no want to receive cookies, you may adjust the settings in your internet browser to reject cookies or to alert you when a cookie is placed on your computer. We do not collect or store any Personal Information via cookies

General Internet User Privacy

In order to gather and aggregate statistical data for our customers, we may from time to time place persistent or temporary cookies on a visitor’s hard drive when visiting a customer’s website. These cookies are not capable of tracking, retaining, or storing any Personal Information, and they are used for no other reason than to gather the same general internet information that is available to all internet service providers, search engines, and websites. Examples of this information include, without limitation, a visitor’s general location based on IP address, information from the visitor’s browser such as browser type, type of operating system, keywords used while searching, websites visited, monitor resolution settings. We may from time to time also authorize and facilitate the use of cookies from trusted third party business partners to gather and aggregate additional, anonymous, and non-Personal Information data from general internet visitors for the purpose of providing our customers with additional information about their viewing audience. We does not gather, retain or store any data from these third party partners. We has also chosen to partner only with businesses that have shown a strong commitment to online privacy and have represented and warranted to Us that any and all data collected on our behalf is non-Personal Information. We do not condone, support, or participate in any activities that could potentially gather, retrieve or store any Personal Information about or from internet users.

Links to Other Websites

Our website contains links to other sites that are not owned or controlled by Us. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such third party websites and this Policy does not govern such other websites or your use of them. This Policy applies only to information collected by our website. We encourage you to be aware when you leave our site and to read the privacy policies of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information.

  1. . For a comprehensive list of definitions and what constitutes “personally identifiable information” please visit http://www.w3.org/TR/1998/WD-P3P10-harmonization-19980330
  2. . For more information Regarding Cookies please see – http://www.bbbonline.org/UnderstandingPrivacy/toolbox/cookies.asp

Additional Information Regarding Online Privacy Can Be Found At:

Cookies & 3rd Party Advertisements

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit

<http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp.>
